opt-intelligence.com 2019-05-24

# Privacy Policy - Opt-Intelligence

## Overview

This website located at www.opt-intelligence.com (this “Website”) is owned and operated by Opt-Intelligence, Inc. We recognize the importance of privacy to you and the other users of the Opt-Intelligence services (the “Services”) and this Website. Opt-Intelligence is providing this notice to explain our online information practices. This Privacy Policy applies only to the collection, use and storage of data collected by us in the course of providing the Services and this Website and does not apply to any other data collected by us online or offline.

As used in this Privacy Policy, “Opt-Intelligence,” “we” and “us” include Opt-Intelligence, Inc. and any third-party vendors we hire to assist in the administration of this Website, the processing or handling of customer information, or otherwise in connection with the Services. These vendors are required to maintain the confidentiality of users’ information and are prohibited from using it for any purpose other than as described in this Privacy Policy.

## The Opt-Intelligence Services

Opt-Intelligence provides Services enabling businesses to monetize their websites and mobile apps with paid advertising, and enabling advertisers to reach the users of those websites and mobile apps. Websites, mobile websites and mobile apps may be referred to as “digital properties” in this Privacy Policy. The Services link companies that collect or enable collection of consumer data on their digital properties with companies that want to collect consumer data in a permission-based manner. The Services allow consumers visiting digital properties to explicitly request that their registration data be sent to one or more advertisers presenting offer(s) using the Services. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, “Publisher Clients” means businesses seeking to monetize their digital properties using the Services, and “Advertiser Clients” means marketers seeking to collect consumer data using the Services.

## You May Opt In to Advertiser Offers

The Services allow you, as a visitor or a registrant on a Publisher Client’s digital property, to view, request and receive special offers provided by our Advertiser Clients. Offers displayed to users of digital properties using the Services may be referred to as “Offers” in this Privacy Policy. When you visit a digital property of a Publisher Client, you may be presented with an offer placement or offer page displaying one or more special Offers from Advertiser Clients. To select an Offer, simply click on the box or “yes” radio button adjacent to the Offer, or otherwise select a positive response in the manner indicated. You can select some of the Offers presented to you, all of the Offers, or none of them—it’s entirely up to you.

## How Opt-Intelligence Receives, Uses and Discloses Your Personal Information

When you visit or register on the digital property of a Publisher Client, the Publisher Client may transfer, subject to its own privacy policy, your personal information and certain non-personal information to Opt-Intelligence. Additionally, if you select an Offer, we may invite you to provide more information by typing directly into a form provided in the offer unit.

By selecting/opting-in an Advertiser Client’s Offer, you authorize Opt-Intelligence to pass the information that you have submitted as part of that opt-in process, including your personal information, to that Advertiser Client. If you do not opt in to any Offers presented, your information transferred to Opt-Intelligence, if any, will be deleted from the Opt-Intelligence servers in accordance with our then current policies and procedures with no further action by you. We strongly encourage you to review the privacy policies of each applicable Advertiser Client before selecting Offers. Opt-Intelligence does not control the use of your personal information by Advertiser Clients.

From time to time, as you opt in to certain Offers via an offer placement or offer page, Opt-Intelligence may request additional personal information from you so that you may participate in optional surveys, contests or other promotional programs. You may choose to provide the additional information to Opt-Intelligence. The additional information may be shared with third parties.

As further protection for you, Opt-Intelligence may send you automated e-mails confirming your Offer selections. If you decide you do not wish to receive information from an Advertiser Client, simply opt out of the applicable offer by following the directions included in the applicable confirmation e-mail message. If you opt out of the offer in this manner, your personal information will be deleted from the Opt-Intelligence servers in accordance with our then current policies and procedures and will not thereafter be sent to the applicable Advertiser Client. If your information has already been sent to the Advertiser Client, Opt-Intelligence will send a notice of your opt-out to the applicable Advertiser Client. In every case where Opt-Intelligence sends an automated confirmation e-mail, you will be instructed how to contact the Advertiser Client directly.

By using this website or selecting one or more Offers on an offer placement or offer page, (1) you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal and non-personal information as described in this Privacy Policy, the privacy policy of the Publisher Client, and the privacy policy of the Advertiser Client, and (2) you agree to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not consent and agree to the practices described and terms of this Privacy Policy, you may not access this website or select any Offers.

We do not use your personal information for purposes other than as described in this Privacy Policy. We have the right to share your personally identifying information with any third party, (1) as required by law, (2) to protect and defend the rights of Opt-Intelligence, a Publisher Client, an Advertiser Client or any other user of the Services, (3) as incident to a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution, bankruptcy or similar event without your consent or approval and without notice to you, (4) under circumstances we believe reasonably necessary to protect the personal safety of users of the Services or the public, or (5) as is otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. Opt-Intelligence adheres to applicable industry self-regulatory principles.

Because neither Opt-Intelligence nor our Publisher Clients have direct control over the content of Advertiser Clients’ offers or the quality of the goods or services offered by Advertiser Clients, you acknowledge and agree that neither Opt-Intelligence nor any Publisher Client is responsible for and in no way guarantees or endorses: (1) the availability of offers offered by Advertiser Clients; or (2) the goods or services offered by Advertiser Clients. Accordingly, you acknowledge and agree that neither Opt-Intelligence nor any Publisher Client shall be responsible or liable to you in any manner, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or allegedly caused by or in connection with use of or reliance on the content of any Offer or any digital property of an Advertiser Client and/or the quality of any goods or services offered by or through any offer or any digital property of an Advertiser Client.

Because neither Opt-Intelligence nor our Advertiser Clients have direct control over the content of Publisher Clients’ digital properties, you acknowledge and agree that neither Opt-Intelligence nor any Advertiser Client shall be responsible or liable to you in any manner, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or allegedly caused by or in connection with use of or reliance on the content of any digital property of a Publisher Client and/or the quality of any goods or services offered by or through any digital property of a Publisher Client.

## Opt-Intelligence Seeks to Deliver Relevant Offers

We receive data from various sources that helps us deliver Offers and generally make our Services better. We may use all of the information we have in order to serve Offers that are more relevant to you, so that you are presented with Offers that you may find interesting. For example, this information includes data about your interactions with Offers, data about other users’ interactions with Offers, certain information you provide to Publisher Clients or directly to us, and information about your demographics, interests and offline activity provided by our trusted third-party partners. We hope this increases the usefulness of Offers for you.

Advertiser Clients may define the target audience for their Offers by location, demographics, interests, purchase behavior and any other information we receive or infer about users. For example, an Advertiser Client may choose to display its Offer only to 18-to-35-year-old women who live in Los Angeles and are interested in sports. If an Advertiser Client chooses to target its audience, we enable opt-ins to its Offer only from people who meet criteria selected by the Advertiser Client.

When an Advertiser Client chooses to target its Offer based on the location of its audience, we may use your IP address to determine your geolocation. This helps us serve local Offers and other Offers you might prefer.

## Opt-Intelligence Collects and Uses Non-Personal, Traffic or Click-Stream Data and Pixel Tags

Data about traffic and usage is not personally identifying or identifiable, and is not supplemented or combined with personally identifying or identifiable information by Opt-Intelligence. Opt-Intelligence may share the non-personal, traffic or click-stream information it collects with certain third parties, but only in anonymous form. For example, we may tell an Advertiser Client that a certain number of people viewed its offer. Opt-Intelligence collects non-personal information about the Publisher Client’s digital property from which you were presented an offer placement or offer page and may share that information with both Advertiser Clients and Publisher Clients. In addition, Opt-Intelligence uses non-personal, traffic or click-stream information to better design and market the Services and to better target Offers to users of digital properties. Opt-Intelligence uses pixel tags (also called clear gifs) to note some of the Advertiser Client websites you visit in relation to the Offers you select. The information collected by Opt-Intelligence through the use of these pixel tags is not personally identifiable.

## Cookies

We may employ both first-party and third-party cookies. Cookies are bits of information that are placed by a website in a storage place on your computer. If you do not want cookies, your Web browser likely includes an option that allows you to not accept and/or to delete them.

## Security of Data Stored by Opt-Intelligence

Opt-Intelligence has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. While we make reasonable efforts to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third parties from illegally obtaining this information. You should consider any communication that you transmit to us (such as personally identifiable or other data, questions or answers, comments, or suggestions) as non-confidential, and you agree that neither Opt-Intelligence, nor any Publisher Client, nor any Advertiser Client shall be liable or responsible if any information about you is intercepted and used by an unintended recipient.

## Collection of Personally Identifying Information from or about Children

Opt-Intelligence uses reasonable efforts not to collect, use or disclose personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. Neither the Services nor the offers presented on an offer page or via an offer placement are targeted at children under the age of 13.

## International Users

Personal data that you have voluntarily entered electronically is delivered to servers located in the United States in connection with the Services. By using this Website, or by selecting an Offer, you consent to the transfer of your personal and non-personal data and to the use of your personal and non-personal data as described in this Privacy Policy, the privacy policy of the applicable Publisher Client and the privacy policy of the applicable Advertiser Client.

## Changes to This Privacy Policy

Opt-Intelligence may, from time to time in its sole discretion, change or modify this Privacy Policy. Any changes or modification will be effective upon posting of the revisions at www.opt-intelligence.com. Opt-Intelligence may post changes or modifications to referenced policies and guidelines without your approval, and may determine in its sole discretion whether and when any such changes apply to you.

## Privacy Choice

We are committed to giving you a simple way to control how Offers are targeted to you. If you no longer wish to be presented with Offers targeted to you using information provided by our third-party data partners, simply send an e-mail to [privacy@opt-intelligence.com](mailto:privacy@opt-intelligence.com) with the subject line “Opt Out of Third-Party Audience Targeting,” and include your e-mail address and full name in the e-mail body. Your opt-out request will take effect within 30 days and will prevent us from targeting Offers to you in the future using third-party data associated with the e-mail address provided in the body of your opt-out request.

## Request or Correct Your Personally Identifying Information

To request a copy of your personally identifiable information stored by Opt-Intelligence, please send an e-mail containing your request to [privacy@opt-intelligence.com](mailto:privacy@opt-intelligence.com) with the subject line “Information Request.” Provide your e-mail address and full name in the e-mail body. We may request additional information from you in order to process your request. You may then request that we correct or delete your personally identifiable information using procedures we will specify in an e-mail message to you.

## Contact Opt-Intelligence

We welcome your questions and feedback. If you have any questions or concerns about anything in this Privacy Policy, or you think someone other than you may have opted in to an Offer using your information, please contact Opt-Intelligence by mail or e-mail using the following address information:

Business Affairs  
Opt-Intelligence, Inc.

Opt-Intelligence

401 Park Ave South, 10th Floor

New York, NY 10016

Email: [privacy@opt-intelligence.com](mailto:privacy@opt-intelligence.com)

This Privacy Policy was last revised on and is effective as of June 23, 2014.
